Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪إن العهد يُعتز به في كل الأوقات♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=خارج الحلقة=
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
Grandfather, drink more.
جدو اشرب أكثر.
This dish was prepared by Mr. Yunhao.
تم إعداد هذا الطبق بواسطة السيد يونهاو.
Yunhao, your cooking skills are amazing!
يونهاو، مهاراتك في الطبخ مذهلة!
Yunqing, learn from Yunhao
Yunqing، تعلم من Yunhao
and cook me some delicious dishes.
وأطبخ لي بعض الأطباق اللذيذة.
If I ever master cooking,
إذا أتقنت الطبخ يومًا ما،
Yunhao will have to quit
سيتعين على يونهاو الاستقالة
as the family chef.
كطاهٍ للعائلة.
Nonsense!
هراء!
You're about to be a father,
أنت على وشك أن تصبح أبًا،
yet still talking nonsense.
ولا زال يتكلم هراء.
Eat up, everyone.
تناولوا الطعام جميعاً.
We haven't
نحن لم نفعل
gathered to have a meal
اجتمعوا لتناول وجبة طعام
for a long time.
لفترة طويلة.
Today is a joyous occasion.
اليوم هو مناسبة سعيدة.
Yunqing, Yunhao.
يون تشينغ، يونهاو.
Let's make a toast
دعونا نصنع نخبًا
to wish Wan good health,
أتمنى لوان الصحة الجيدة،
a safe delivery,
ولادة آمنة
and for adding a new member to the our family.
ولإضافة عضو جديد إلى عائلتنا.
Thank you, Grandfather.
شكرا لك يا جدو.
Yunhao.
يونهاو.
Find me a sister-in-law!
ابحث لي عن أخت زوجي!
Hurry up.
اسرع.
Him?
له؟
He's not grown up yet,
إنه لم يكبر بعد
now still hanging around those pleasure houses all day,
لا أزال أتجول حول تلك المنازل الترفيهية طوال اليوم،
enjoying his carefree life.
يستمتع بحياته الخالية من الهموم.
How could he spare time to find a wife?
كيف يمكنه توفير الوقت للبحث عن زوجة؟
Come on, let's eat.
هيا لنأكل.
Here, let me toast you.
هنا، اسمح لي أن أشرب نخبًا لك.
Yunhao.
يونهاو.
Yunqing.
يونتشينغ.
Drink up!
اشرب!
Yunhao, you are
يونهاو، أنت
at your age,
في عمرك،
not married,
غير متزوج
not chasing career,
عدم ملاحقة المهنة،
what do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
W-What can I do?
س- ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
I've been cowardly since childhood,
لقد كنت جبانًا منذ الطفولة،
not cut out for great things.
غير قادر على القيام بأشياء عظيمة.
I'll just live off the family fortune.
سأعيش على ثروة العائلة فقط.
You have
لديك
the capabilities as the City Lord.
القدرات كزعيم للمدينة.
Here, Yunhao.
هنا، يونهاو.
Here.
هنا.
Bottoms up!
من الأسفل إلى الأعلى!
Let me check. There's some left.
دعني أتحقق، بقي بعض منها.
To be honest...
صراحة...
Go ahead.
تفضل.
I'm tire
انا متعب
of being the City Lord.
كونه سيد المدينة.
I wanted to quit long ago.
لقد أردت الإستقالة منذ زمن طويل.
Yunhao, why don't you take over?
يونهاو، لماذا لا تتولى الأمر؟
Nonsense!
هراء!
Yunhao.
يونهاو.
You are the City Lord.
أنت سيد المدينة.
I'm telling you, you're drunk.
أنا أقول لك، أنت في حالة سكر.
Just focus on being the City Lord.
ركز فقط على كونك سيد المدينة.
Grandfather is watching you.
الجد يراقبك.
Later, let Wan help you back.
لاحقًا، دع وان يساعدك.
I-I should...
ينبغي لي...
Yunhao, another cup!
يونهاو، كوب آخر!
You're drunk.
أنت سكران.
Wan will come get you later.
وان سيأتي ليأخذك لاحقًا.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Yunhao, take care.
يونهاو، اعتني بنفسك.
After the physician treated Mr. Yunhao,
بعد أن عالج الطبيب السيد يونهاو،
and I escorted him out.
ورافقته للخارج.
He said something strange.
لقد قال شيئا غريبا.
Strange?
غريب؟
The physician said
قال الطبيب
Mr. Yunhao's wound
جرح السيد Yunhao
seems to be stabbed
يبدو أنه طُعن
by himself.
بنفسه.
(What am I thinking?)
(ماذا أفكر؟)
(Why would Yunhao harm me?)
(لماذا يؤذيني يونهاو؟)
Husband.
زوج.
I made you this hangover soup.
لقد صنعت لك هذا الحساء للتخلص من آثار الكحول.
Taste good?
طعمه جيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Are you drunk?
هل انت سكران؟
I can drink more than Yunhao.
أستطيع أن أشرب أكثر من يونهاو.
Let's go for a walk.
دعنا نذهب في نزهة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
For the children?
من أجل الأطفال؟
That design is beautiful.
هذا التصميم جميل .
Almost sold out.
تم بيعها تقريبا.
How much?
كم ثمن؟
Three coins. Pretty.
ثلاث عملات معدنية. جميلة.
Come see the lanterns!
تعالوا وانظروا إلى الفوانيس!
Children love them.
الأطفال يحبونهم.
We have all kinds of shapes here.
لدينا جميع أنواع الأشكال هنا.
I wish time could freeze at this moment,
أتمنى أن يتوقف الزمن عند هذه اللحظة،
so we could be this happy forever.
حتى نتمكن من أن نكون سعداء إلى الأبد.
Then you better treat me well,
إذن من الأفضل أن تعاملني بشكل جيد،
or I'll run away.
أو سأهرب.
You won't.
لن تفعل ذلك.
I am sure about that.
أنا متأكد من ذلك.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
You kid.
أنت طفل.
Here, take it.
هنا، خذها.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Mother.
الأم.
Candied haws.
الزعرور المسكر.
Candied haws again?
الزعرور المسكر مرة أخرى؟
Yunqing, when our child is born,
يونتشينغ، عندما يولد طفلنا،
we'll be happier than them.
سوف نكون أكثر سعادة منهم.
You love children so much?
هل تحب الأطفال كثيرًا؟
Then have a few more.
ثم تناول المزيد.
You think giving birth
هل تعتقد أن الولادة
is that easy?
هل هذا سهل؟
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
I'll give birth to them, okay?
سألدهم، حسنًا؟
Fine, you'll do it.
حسنا، سوف تفعل ذلك.
Try having one then.
حاول أن تمتلك واحدة إذن.
I'll do it.
سأفعل ذلك.
Lanterns!
الفوانيس!
What's the occasion?
ما هي المناسبة؟
So many lanterns!
الكثير من الفوانيس!
Madam.
سيدتي.
The Lantern Festival is in half a month.
مهرجان الفوانيس بعد نصف شهر.
Lantern Festival?
مهرجان الفوانيس؟
Look, I bought you a jade pendant.
انظر، لقد اشتريت لك قلادة من اليشم.
Wan, what's wrong?
وان، ما الخطب؟
Yunqing, I'm not feeling well.
يونتشينغ، أنا لا أشعر أنني على ما يرام.
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Alright. Sorry.
حسناً، آسف.
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
What's with you today?
ماذا معك اليوم؟
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
At today's dinner,
في عشاء اليوم،
Mu Yunqing acted strange.
تصرف مو يون تشينغ بشكل غريب.
I think we can't keep this hidden much longer.
أعتقد أننا لا نستطيع إبقاء هذا الأمر مخفيًا لفترة أطول.
Today I kept thinking
اليوم بقيت أفكر
if I hadn't fought for this position,
لو لم أقاتل من أجل هذا المنصب،
we might've had our own child
ربما كان من الممكن أن يكون لدينا طفلنا الخاص
and our own courtyard by now.
وفناءنا الخاص الآن.
Or even,
أو حتى،
our own piece of land.
قطعة أرض خاصة بنا.
Yunhao, no matter what happens,
يونهاو، بغض النظر عما يحدث،
I'll always stay by your side.
سأبقى بجانبك دائمًا.
Okay.
تمام.
(I'll definitely help you eliminate Mu Yunqing)
(سوف أساعدك بالتأكيد في التخلص من مو يونتشينغ)
(and reclaim the City Lord Token.)
(واستعادة رمز سيد المدينة.)
You poisoned my lady,
لقد سممت سيدتي،
yet you came to me now?
ولكنك أتيت إلي الآن؟
Aren't you afraid I'll kill you?
ألا تخاف أن أقتلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
The Yu family is just merchants.
عائلة يو مجرد تجار.
What makes a skilled person like you obey them
ما الذي يجعل شخصًا ماهرًا مثلك يطيعهم؟
is nothing
ليس شيئا
but sufficient payment.
ولكن الدفع كافي.
Think you can buy me off with this little?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع شرائي بهذا القليل؟
This is just the deposit.
هذا مجرد الوديعة.
Tenfold after success.
عشرة أضعاف بعد النجاح.
What do you want me to do?
ماذا تريدني أن أفعل؟
Yu Yingwan is such a nuisance.
يو Yingwan هو مثل هذا الإزعاج.
You know what to do.
أنت تعرف ماذا تفعل.
Working with you is risky.
العمل معك محفوف بالمخاطر.
I want to meet your master.
أريد مقابلة سيدك.
Deal.
اتفاق.
City Lord, terrible!
سيد المدينة، فظيع!
Madam has gone missing!
لقد اختفت السيدة!
Lady.
سيدة.
Liu Bingmo, where are we?
ليو بينغمو، أين نحن؟
No idea. I just woke up too.
ليس لدي أي فكرة. لقد استيقظت للتو أيضًا.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Are we kidnapped?
هل نحن مختطفون؟
Maybe last night's soup was poisoned.
ربما كان حساء الليلة الماضية مسموما.
The soup was poisoned?
هل كان الحساء مسموما؟
Well, back-to-back.
حسنًا، ظهرًا لظهر.
I'll untie you.
سأفكك.
Hurry.
عجل.
Will this work?
هل سيعمل هذا؟
Let's try.
دعونا نحاول.
Trying to escape?
تحاول الهروب؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Seeking death!
أبحث عن الموت!
♪Winter snow waltzes before the courtyard♪
♪رقصة ثلوج الشتاء أمام الفناء♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪القصور لا ترحم♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪يتطلب الأمر الكثير من الشجاعة♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪لإعادة تتبع كل خطوة♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪همسات الذاكرة، أحلام أو وهم♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪الفراشات تتسلق الجبال من أجل الحب♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪يموت قبل الزهور♪
♪You seem so distant, yet right before my eyes♪
♪تبدو بعيدًا جدًا، ومع ذلك، أمام عيني مباشرة♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪لعبة شطرنج، مصير الصراع♪
♪I dream of standing with you, side by side♪
♪أحلم بالوقوف معك جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪إذا قابلتني وجها لوجه♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪سأموت دون ندم واحد♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪لدموعك وعناقك♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪